- 怎么了?
- 我忘了拿吉他
好吧，没问题
拿去吧
- 什么?
- 你要聊聊吗?
你来的不是时候
- 你跟钱德…
- 没错
- 要我帮你们伴奏吗?
- 不必
菲比，你好吗?
你问了一个很有趣的问题 钱德.宾
天啊，你请人帮你按摩? 你从来不让我帮你按摩
菲比，我可以解释
听着…
天啊，我得学怎么说慌
你说过你讨厌按摩
去买邮票，拿干洗的衣服 别让菲比进来
你背着我这么做多久了?
- 亚丽珊卓…
- 它还有名字?
菲比，别生气
好吧，太迟了，我要走了来吧，钱德，我们走
我以为我…
对，管它的
老友记 Friends S08E14 本集播出：秘密储物间
再报一次 加油，快好了
我很高兴我们能在一起 我们要生孩子了，我爱你
我也爱你
我希望现在说这个不会不是时候…
你是我最棒的性伴侣
你随时都能那么说
来吧，再推一次再推一次
好了
你们的漂亮宝宝 恭喜
希望你做爸爸比做朋友称职
乔伊
- 发生了什么事?
- 快来摸摸我的肚子
- 这是宝宝第一次踢我
- 真的吗?
对
你知道吗? 或许你…
或许你该走过来 我没有穿裤子
天啊
太不可思议了
她踢得好厉害 她像是…
那个讨厌的女足球员是谁?
- 米亚汉姆?
- 米亚汉姆
- 太神奇了
- 抓住你的床单，乔伊
抱歉
嘿，宝贝
巴伯跟菲伊宾送我们结婚礼物 他们不喜欢我们，对吧?
谁说买不到六块以下的高级鸡尾酒碗?
- 或许我们能把它退回去
- 我们要把它迟到哪里去?
何不从阳台把它丢到街上?
我们不能那么做 万一他们来看我们呢?
我们过桥去看我15年没看过的阿姨跟姨丈
给他们一个惊喜要他们送我们大一点的鸡尾酒碗
我们为什么不找个地方放它?
放在那个柜子里?
那是放罐头食物的 你忘了每样东西都要放在定位吗?
浴室旁边的柜子呢?
- 让我来吧
- 不，我来就行了
你得放轻松 偶尔把事情交给我来做
上锁了，你得帮帮我 为什么上锁了?
没有为什么 我把私人物品放在那里
我搬到这里来一阵子了 从来没看过里面的东西
里面放了什么?
女人的东西
别想用女人的东西来唬我
那里面没有你喜欢的东西 如果你爱我，忘了这件事
- 好吧
- 谢谢
我爱你
钱德 今天天气真好，是你
如果有帮助的话亚丽珊卓已经帮她按摩了三年
我说如果有帮助的话
你为什么不让我帮你按摩?
我会无法放松 你是我的朋友，我得脱光衣服
我们住在一起那么多年 我看过你没穿衣服
那不一样，我们是室友 那是什么时候的事?
我对人体很好奇
你可以了解 为什么我会觉得很奇怪
我是专家 我真的很厉害
如果你觉得不舒服，我们就停止给我一个机会，拜托
如果你真的觉得很重要
没错，如果你无法分享你的厨艺 你会有什么感觉?
如果罗斯没办法教我们龙的事他会有什么感觉?
- 是恐龙
- 都一样
罗斯，宝宝在踢
什么? 是吗?
她现在没有在踢我
虽然我们很想看到你再做一次
什么时候? 发生了什么事?
昨晚我跑到乔伊的房间 他在睡觉
我没有做梦
天啊，宝宝会踢了 真的是太棒了
我希望我可以摸到宝宝第一次踢你的样子
如果你真的想摸 我的肚子正在咕咕叫
我不要，但你看起来有母性光辉
我不想再错过宝宝的事了 这是我新的呼叫器号码
只要发生跟怀孕有关的事立刻通知我
我不在乎那是凌晨三点 而你想吃冰淇淋
我能抄一份吗?
- 你裹着床单吗?
- 对
好了，我们开始吧
力道还可以吧?
很不错，菲比，你真的很厉害
很明显，谢谢你的夸奖
- 那一点都不奇怪，对吧?
- 没错
没错，好好享受吧
对
- 对
- 好吧
天啊，菲比
就是那样，就是那里
我发誓 我没有试着打开你的柜子
莫妮卡管你很严，对吧? 你在做什么?
莫妮卡有秘密衣柜 她不肯让我看它
- 为什么?
- 我不知道，她在隐瞒什么?
我不知道
我敢说是理查
- 什么?
- 在你说我错了之前
我要问你一件事
你最后一次看到他是什么时候的事?
她为什么要把理查关在那里?
我不知道…
或者她想鱼与熊掌兼得
你是“熊掌” 理查只是“鱼”
- 那就是你想出来的理论?
- 对
- 或是…
- 又来了
我看过一部电影里有一扇门 没有人知道里面藏了什么
最后他们把门打开后好几百万只虫跑了出来
开起了人肉宴会
尊重你老婆的隐私 不会要你的命
塞满虫的笨衣柜
乔伊，我觉得怪怪的 那不是好事，我不…
我妹妹怀孕时…
她们都觉得怪怪的 结果根本没事
- 真的吗?
- 当然
但我们得到医院检查一下 我会呼叫罗斯
瑞秋，看着我，一切都会没事的 相信我，握着我的手，我们走吧
我快骨折了
还好我们要去医院
- 打开它
- 你为什么
小心你的脚 到处都有虫
- 结果呢?
- 她没事
她出现不规则的子宫收缩 那是子宫壁出现中度不适的现象
中度不适? 我想你也出现过那种现象
- 一切都很正常?
- 对
- 没有危险?
收缩虽然会不舒服 但她没事
谢谢你，医生 谢谢你这么温和冷静
我一点都不冷静 我从来没有这么害怕过
- 你说一切都会没事的
- 我知道什么? 我不是医生
- 但一切都没事，我没事
- 你确定?
对，我真希望那个医生的子宫也会收缩
中度不适 他到底在胡说什么
- 没事吧?
- 没事
你呼叫我说“赶到医院来”发生了什么事?
-她出现不规则的子宫收缩
-什么“布拉克斯通・希克斯”子宫收缩
那没什么大不了的 很多女人都不会有感觉
没有子宫的人不能置评
糖果是怎么一回事?
你呼叫我时我在电影院买零食
- 你自己去看电影?
- 蒙娜
- 我得回检查室去
- 发生了什么事?
- 我得…
- 不，告诉我，怎么了?
听着，我忘了穿内裤
谢谢你送她来医院
别担心，那没有什么大不了的
但应该是由我送她来 我是孩子的爸
- 这是不规则收缩的资料
- 谢谢
你送她过来是对的
你会是个好爸爸
我没有这家伙厉害 他买了“灯芯草”（赫氏公司生产的一种糖果）
- 一定会有办法
- 别紧张，寇克船长（《星际迷航》中柯克船长的口头语）
- 你有小别针吗?
- 有
不，等一下 我不是九岁的小女孩
为什么你投球的时候很像?
- 或许莫妮卡有小别针
- 对，“莫妮卡”
你暗恋瑞秋的事 怎么了?
真的很不错 我应该随时准备好自杀
你这么快就发现了
我希望我从没有爱过瑞秋 我希望一切能恢复正常
我喜欢跟她一起住帮助她生产 真的很有趣
但我觉得罗斯会觉得自己被排除在外
我送瑞秋去医院时 医生以为我是孩子的爸
你应该看看罗斯的表情
我不知道我在做什么 我只知道我越开锁得越紧
- 你想拿信用卡打开它吗?
- 好点子
罗斯很难过?
- 我觉得很难过
- 那不是你的错
你要怎么做? 不送她去医院？ 你没有做错事
但你不该爱上怀了他孩子的女人
好了
理查，如果你在里面麻烦你把信用卡还我
我得告诉你昨天真的很棒按摩感觉很舒服
不，我了解
- 我们能每星期按摩一次吗
- 好吧
但你应该知道 我的时薪调成两百块了
- 我是说五百块
- 什么?
- 六百块
怎么回事?
我按摩你时你会发出性爱叫声
那把我吓坏了之后我想弄痛你，你叫得更大声
你疯了 我的叫声一点都不淫荡
这一点都不淫荡?
天啊
你在看什么?
我是说，嗨
所以亚丽珊卓帮我按摩时都会戴耳塞
那不是因为她讨厌恩雅
这真的是太丢脸了 我永远都不会再按摩了
别让这件事害你放弃按摩
我有很多客人也会发出那种叫声
- 真的吗?
- 他们不是客人，他们是情人
我们再试一次再来找我，我们会想出办法的
- 你确定?
- 对
- 我猜是吧
- 太棒了，对不起
你听到你喜欢的声音了吗?
罗斯，你看 我学到新把戏了
如果一只手放在裤袋里 你和乔伊没两样
我帮你买了午餐
你真的太贴心了，真好吃
- 你放了脑黄瓜吗?
- 对
什么? 瑞秋，怎么了?
- 发生了什么事?
- 我帮她带了腌黄瓜鲍鱼三明治
腌黄瓜? 那会让她想吐
让她吃腌黄瓜就像让我吃沙拉
抱歉，我不知道，你还好吗?
我没事，但我不在的时候麻烦谁解决掉它
我在吃了
我不该让她吐的
- 谁都可以做出这种事
- 你就不会，你了解她
我什么都不懂，而我是孩子的爸
我希望我能多参与一点
如果有人在帮我纪录的话 我绝不会再吃金枪鱼了
我能跟你们谈一谈吗?
- 可以啊
- 怎么了?
坐吧 我想谈谈我们的情况
你要跟我们分手吗?
我要说的是…
因为我跟瑞秋一起住 我参与了很多事
罗斯错过了一切，所以
怎么了?
你们两个应该住在一起
你要我搬出来? 你不要我住在这里？
不，我喜欢跟你一起住 只不过…
如果你需要室友他最好是孩子的爸
乔伊，我想罗斯不希望 我搬过去干扰他的生活
或许他想那么做
我很乐意照顾你跟宝宝
我们可试试看先试一阵子
- 但那是你跟我
- 我们不会有感情牵扯
我在和蒙娜交往，该死，蒙娜
我跟她约好一小时前要见面 我是怎么了?
你们觉得呢?
跟孩子的爸住在一起对我们来说那太传统了
对，但是你一直都喜欢我的公寓
我还有空房间 你还会有放鞋专柜
你真的很了解你的听众
- 我不知道，那很疯狂吗?
- 不
乔伊，这是个聪明点子
我该想到的
- 就这么办吧
- 真的吗?
瑞秋，那真的是太棒了
你知道吗? 别担心搬家的事
一切都交给我 事实上 我会从现在开始帮你搬家
罗斯，蒙娜
不可思议
还不错 我用我太太的工具
把自己弄成这个样子
我的天啊
你怎么把它打开的?
你很不整洁
- 不，你不该看这个的
- 我娶了弗瑞德・桑福德（《桑福德和他的儿子》中的垃圾场主）
钱德，你不了解
你知道 我喜欢把东西排得整整齐齐的
这些是我无法分类的东西
我不是懒散的太太
我太讲究了，所以
好吧，现在你知道了 我很病态
不，老婆，你不病态 我爱你不是因为你做事有条不紊
不论如何，我都爱你
真的吗?
- 你发誓不会告诉任何人?
- 对
现在我知道了，如果我有多余的东西 我们可以一起用那个柜子吗?
哦... 那只是...
我怕你会把它弄乱
- 嘿
瑞秋搬出去了? 你还好吧?
我要喝几瓶啤酒…
但我把啤酒都丢了 因为瑞秋受不了那个味道
我买了很多加钙的柳橙汁
它已经过期了几星期 所以会有点酸昧
- 你没事吧?
- 你在开玩笑吗? 我棒透了
我好到不能再好，我很好
现在她离开了 我可以做以前不能做的事
譬如…
我又能脱光衣服乱跑了
我可以…
我可以在客厅看色情片
这对我来说是件好事
我喜欢一个人过生活 我喜欢这个样子
我是一匹孤独的野狼
我是个完全孤单的硬汉
永远都是一个人
狼要怎么做才能得到一个拥抱呢?
好了，放轻松
- 加油，再来
- 天啊
你喜欢那样，对吧?
- 对，就是那样
- 你要吗? 我就给你，宝贝
- 菲比
- 对，叫我的名字，快点
现在我要帮你盖上被子
我会有好几个星期不会再跟你说话
- What's up?
- I left my guitar here.
Okay. No problem.
Okay. Here you go.
- What?
- You want to hang out or something?
You caught me at a bad time.
- Are you and Chandler...?
- Exactly.
- Can I play for you?
- No.
Hey, Pheebs, what's up?
You ask an intriguing question, Chandler Bing.
Oh, my God! You're getting a massage?
You never let me massage you.
Phoebe, I can explain.
You see...
God, I gotta get better at lying.
You said you hate massages.
Buy stamps. Pick up dry cleaning.
Don't let Phoebe in.
How long has this been going on?
- Well, Alexandra has...
- It has a name?
Phoebe, don't get upset.
Okay. Oh, too late! I'm leaving.
Come on, Chandler, let's go.
Well, I thought I'd...
Yeah, what the hell.
The One With The Secret Closet
One more push. Come on, we're almost there.
I'm happy things worked out for us and we're having this baby. I love you.
I love you too.
I hope it's not an inappropriate time to say...
...you're the best sex I've ever had.
That's always appropriate.
Okay, come on, one more push. One more push.
There we go.
Here is your beautiful baby.
Congratulations.
I hope you're a better father than you are a friend!
Joey!
- What's going on?
- Come feel my belly.
- The baby's kicking for the first time.
- Really?
Yes.
You know what? Maybe you...
Maybe you should come to me.
I'm not wearing any bottoms.
Oh, my God.
It's unbelievable!
Wow, she is kicking so much. She's like...
Who's that annoying girl soccer player?
- Mia Hamm?
- Mia Hamm!
- It's amazing.
- One hand on the sheet, Joe.
Sorry.
Hey, babe.
We got a wedding gift from Bob and Faye Bing.
They don't like us, do they?
Who says you can't get a nice punch bowl for under $6?
- Maybe we can take it back.
- Where would we return it?
How about to the street, from the balcony?
We can't do that. What if they come by for a visit?
Let's cross that bridge when my aunt and uncle who I haven't seen in 15 years...
...drop by unexpectedly and demand a giant bowl of punch.
Why don't we just find a place for it?
In that cabinet?
That's for canned goods.
Have you forgotten everything from orientation?
How about the closet by the bathroom?
- Okay. Let me do it.
- No, I'll do it.
You have to relax and let me take care of things once in a while.
It's locked. You have to help me.
Why is it locked?
No reason. I keep private things in there.
I've been here a while, and I've never seen what's in there.
What is in there?
Feminine stuff.
Don't try to make me uncomfortable with feminine stuff!
Nothing in there concerns you.
If you love me, you'll just let it go.
- Fine.
- Thank you.
Love you.
Hello, Chandler.
Lovely day, huh? You.
If it helps, Alexandra's only been massaging her for three years.
If! I said, if it helps.
Why won't you let me massage you?
I'd be self-conscious. You're my friend.
I'd be naked.
We lived together for years.
I've seen you naked.
That's different.
We were roommates. And when?
I'm curious about the human body.
You can understand why this would be weird.
I'm a professional and I'm really good.
If you're uncomfortable, we can stop.
Give me a chance. Please?
If it means that much to you.
It does. How would you feel if you couldn't share your cooking?
Or how Ross would feel if he couldn't teach us about dragons.
- Dinosaurs.
- Potato, potahto.
Ross, the baby's kicking.
What? It is?
It's not kicking now.
Although we would love to see you do that again.
When? What happened?
Last night. I went into Joey's room, and he was sleeping.
A dreamless sleep.
My God, the baby's kicking.
That's great.
I wish I would have been there to feel the kicking for the first time.
I got some stuff going on if you want to feel.
I'll pass, but you look radiant.
I don't want to miss any more baby stuff.
Here's my pager number.
Anytime anything pregnancy-related happens, use it.
I don't care if it's 3 a. M. And you want ice cream.
Can I get a copy of that?
- Are you under the sheet?
- Yes.
Great, let's begin.
How's the pressure?
It's nice. Wow, Phoebe, you are good.
Stating the obvious, but thank you.
- And it's not weird, is it?
- No.
That's right, you just enjoy.
Oh, yeah!
- Oh, yeah!
- Okay.
Oh, God, Phoebe!
That's it! That's it, right there!
I wasn't trying to open your closet, I swear.
Monica runs a pretty tight ship here, doesn't she?
What are you doing?
Monica has a secret closet.
She won't let me see it.
- Why not?
- I don't know! What's she hiding?
I don't know.
I bet it's Richard.
- What?
- Before you say I'm wrong...
...let me ask you something.
When was the last time you saw him?
Why would she keep Richard in here?
Off the top of my head...
...maybe she's having her cake and eating it too.
You being the "cake," Richard being the "too."
- That was off the top of your head?
- Yeah.
- Or...
- And here we go.
I saw a movie where there was a door.
Nobody knew what was behind it.
When they finally got it open, millions of bugs came pouring out...
...and they feasted on human flesh!
It wouldn't kill you to respect your wife's privacy!
Stupid closet full of bugs!
Joey, something feels weird and not good weird. I don't...
When my sisters were pregnant...
...they got weird feelings and it was always nothing.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
But we'll stop by the hospital just to be sure. I'll page Ross.
Rach, look at me. Everything's fine.
Trust me. Take my hand. Here we go.
Crushing bones!
Good thing we're going to a hospital.
- Open it.
- Why'd you...
Watch your feet.
There's bugs everywhere.
- So?
- She's fine.
She had Braxton Hicks contractions.
Mild discomfort in the uterine wall.
Mild discomfort?
I take it you've had one of these Braxton thingies?
- Everything's normal?
- Yes.
- There's no danger?
- No.
Contractions can be unnerving, but she's fine.
Thank you, doctor.
And thank you for being nice and calm.
I wasn't calm!
I've never been more scared in my life.
- You said everything was okay.
- What do I know? I'm not a doctor.
- But everything is okay. I'm fine.
- You sure?
Yes. I got half a mind to contract that doctor's uterus.
Mild discomfort!
What's he talking about?
- Is everything okay?
- Yes.
Your page said, "Come to the hospital." What happened?
Something called Braxton Hicks contraction.
That's no big deal.
Most women don't feel them.
No uterus, no opinion.
What's with the candy?
I was at the concession stand at the movies.
- You went to the movies by yourself?
- Mona!
- I gotta go back in there.
- What's wrong?
- I just gotta...
- No, really, tell me. What's up?
Look, I forgot my underwear.
Thanks for bringing her to the hospital.
Don't worry about it. No big deal.
But still, it should have been me.
I'm the dad.
- Here's information on Braxton Hicks.
- Thanks.
You did the right thing by bringing her in.
You'll make a wonderful father.
Hey, not as good as this guy. He brought Twizzlers.
- There has got to be a way.
- Easy there, Captain Kirk.
- Do you have a bobby pin?
- Yeah.
Oh, no, wait. I'm not a 9-year-old girl.
Then why do you throw like one?
- Maybe Monica has a bobby pin.
- Oh, sure, "Monica."
So how's the inappropriate crush on Rachel coming?
Really good. I should be ready to kill myself any day now.
Well, you sure found that quick.
I wish I didn't feel this way about Rachel.
I wish things could be normal.
I love living with her, and helping out with the baby is amazing.
But now I think Ross feels left out.
When I took Rachel to the hospital,
the doctor thought I was the father.
You should have seen the look on Ross' face.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
For all I know, I'm locking it more.
- You try opening it with a credit card?
- That's a good idea.
So Ross is kind of bummed, huh?
- I feel terrible.
- It's not your fault.
What are you gonna do, not take her?
You're doing nothing wrong.
Except for harboring love for the woman carrying his baby.
Well, there is that.
Richard, if you're in there, could you pass me my credit card?
I gotta tell you, yesterday was amazing.
That massage felt so good.
No, I got that.
- Can we make it a weekly appointment?
- Okay.
You should know though, I've raised my rates to $200 an hour.
- I mean 500.
- What? - 600.
What's going on?
You make sex noises when you get massaged.
It freaked me out. After a while, I tried to hurt you.
It spurred you on.
You're crazy. There's nothing sexual about the noises I make.
There's nothing sexual about this?
Oh, God!
What are you looking at?
I mean, hi.
Oh, that's why Alexandra wears earplugs when she gives me a massage.
It's not because she hates Enya.
This is embarrassing.
I'm never getting a massage again.
Don't let this stop you from getting massages.
I have lots of clients that make those noises.
- Really?
- Well, not clients. Lovers.
We'll try it again.
Come back, and we'll work through it.
- You sure?
- Yes.
- I guess.
- Great! Now, if you'll just excuse me.
So did you hear something you liked?
Hey, Ross, check it out!
I learned a new trick.
You know, if you stick one hand down your pants, you're the spitting image of Joey.
Hey, I brought you some lunch.
Oh, that's so sweet of you. Oh, yum.
- Did you put pickles on this?
- Well, yeah.
What? What? Rach, what?
- What's going on?
- I made her tuna with pickle.
Pickle? Pickle makes her sick.
Giving her pickle is like giving me salad.
I'm sorry, I didn't know. You okay?
I'm fine, but someone make sure it's gone when I get out?
I'm on it!
I shouldn't be the one making her throw up.
- It could happen to anyone.
- Not to you. You know this stuff.
I don't know any of it and I'm the father.
I wish I could be more involved, you know?
Well, if anyone is keeping score, I no longer eat tuna.
Can I talk to you guys for a second?
- Yeah.
- What's up?
Sit down. I wanna talk about our situation.
Are you breaking up with us?
The thing is...
...because I live with Rachel, I'm here for a lot of stuff.
And Ross is missing everything. So...
Yeah?
You two should live together.
Are you asking me to move?
You don't want me here?
No, I love living with you.
It just seems that...
...if you're gonna have a roommate, it may as well be the father.
But, Joey, I don't think Ross wants me to move in and disrupt his life.
Or he does.
I would love to be around for you and the baby.
We can just try it, like on a temporary basis.
- But it's you and me.
- It wouldn't be anything romantic.
I'm dating Mona. Damn it, Mona!
I was supposed to meet her an hour ago.
What is wrong with me?
So, what do you think?
Living with the father of the baby.
It's a little conventional for us.
Yeah, but hey, hey. You always have liked my building.
And there's more room.
I mean, you could have a closet dedicated to shoes.
Oh, you do know your audience.
- I don't know. Is it crazy?
- No.
Joey, this is a smart idea.
Well, I was due.
- Let's do it.
- Really?
Rach, that's great. That's great.
And you know what? Don't worry about any of the moving.
I'll take care of everything.
In fact, I'll start right now.
Ross, Ross. Mona?
Unbelievable.
Not too shabby. I got this all off myself...
...using my wife's tools.
Oh, my God.
How did you get in there?
You're messy.
- No! You weren't supposed to see this!
- I married Fred Sanford.
Chandler, you don't understand.
You know, how I organize everything, right?
Okay, well this is all of the stuff that doesn't fit into any category.
So you see, I'm not messy.
I'm just so organized that...
Okay, okay, fine! Now you know. I'm sick.
No, honey, you're not sick.
I don't love you because you're organized.
I love you in spite of that.
Really?
- Promise you won't tell anyone?
- Yes.
Now that I know, if I've got extra stuff, can we share the closet?
Well... It's just...
I'm afraid you might mess it up.
- Hey.
So Rachel's all moved out? How you taking it?
I wanted to have a few beers...
...but I got rid of those because Rachel couldn't stand the smell.
I have thrown back a lot of orange juice with calcium.
It's a couple weeks past its expiration date, so it's got a bit of a kick.
- Are you okay?
- You kidding me? Yeah, I'm great.
I'm better than great. I am good.
Now that she's gone, I can do stuff around here that I couldn't do before.
Like...
I can walk around naked again.
I can...
I can watch porn in the living room.
This is good for me.
I like being on my own.
I'm better off this way.
I'm a lone wolf.
A loner. Alone.
All alone. Forever.
What's a wolf gotta do to get a hug around here?
That's it, just relax.
- Come on, more.
- Oh, God!
You like that, don't you?
- Yeah, right there.
- Want it there? Take it there, baby.
- Phoebe?
- Yeah, say my name. Say it.
And now I'm going to cover you back up.
And I won't be speaking with you for several weeks.